Urban Borderlands Records MS083
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Fall 2008, 1990 -- 2008; MS083.006; 1.2 Linear Feet; 27 Digital Object(s)
  - Latin Dance in Somerville - J. Schiff Urban Borderlands 08 Disk 2/2, 2008-10-29 -- 2008-12-08; MS083.006.025.00052; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    J. Schiff Latin Dance in Somerville Urban Borderland 08 Disk 2/2 Side A: Interviews with students at the Welcom Project Wed Oct 29 08 and with Namibia Lebron-Torres Fri Nov 6 and Mon Dec 8 08 Side B: Interview with Namibia Lebron-Torres Fri Nov 6 and Mon Dec 8 08.
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves - Jair Morales and Jessica Martinez, 2008-10-24 -- 2008-10-31; MS083.006.025.00053; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Jair Morales 10/24/08 and Jessica Martinez 10/31/08.
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves - Elias 'Danny' Martinez, 2008; MS083.006.025.00054; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - Painting, Singing and Dancing Ourselves - Luana and Jesus, 2008; MS083.006.025.00055; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    No label.
  - 'This is my Language' - Jessica Sofio Interview Diego Auzman, 2008; MS083.006.025.00056; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - 'This is my Language' - Jessica Sofio Interview Wilbur Zenderos and Raul Gonzales, 2008-10-17 -- 2008-10-31; MS083.006.025.00057; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
    Wilbur Zenderos 10/31/08 and Raul Gonzales 10/17/08
  - 'This is my Language' - Jessica Sofio Interview Elaine Bay, 2008; MS083.006.025.00058; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
  - 'This is my Language' - Jessica Sofio Interview Diego Gozman, 2008; MS083.006.025.00059; Schiff, Julia (Case MS083 Shared 2)
- Content manifestations, 2002 -- 2008; MS083.007; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials generated in the course of making selections available online, including, but not limited to, text transcriptions, audio files, and webpages. Funding for some of these activities was provided by a library Berger Family Technology Transfer Grant in 2004-2005.
  This series is arranged organically.
  - Berger grant digitization project files, 2002 -- 2008; MS083.007.026.00001
    All files were created by DCA staff from existing collection materials described elsewhere in the collection.
    Dept. of Sociology/Anthropology
- Fall 2010, MS083.008; 12 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials from the Fall 2010 semester.
  - Indian and Nepali immigrant businesses in Somerville: a study of growing communities, 2010; MS083.008.027.00001; Daniels, Alexis
  - Word-of-mouth: communication, culture and business in Somerville's Haitian community, 2010; MS083.008.027.00002; Jeremie, Amatoga
  - Somerville's beauty salons: unique spaces of lingustic development, 2010; MS083.008.027.00003; Kokulis, Caroline; Sheehan, Elizabeth
  - A flavor of Haiti in Somerville: a look at the Haitian community in Somerville and how it will be effected by the Green Line Extension Project, 2010; MS083.008.027.00004; Barthelemy, Cassandra
  - South Asian immigrant businesses in Somerville, 2010; MS083.008.027.00005; Lee, Eugenia
  - Korean-American businesses in Somerville, 2010; MS083.008.027.00006; Kim, Jeewon
  - Small businesses in a changing community: Somerville's laundromats, dry cleaners, and tailors, 2010; MS083.008.027.00007; Schwartz, Emily
  - Churches in Somerville: the role of religion in an immigrant city, 2010; MS083.008.027.00008; Bowles, Kaitlyn
  - Brazilian entrepreneurship in Somerville, MA, 2010; MS083.008.027.00009; Christiansen, Katie
  - A brief glimpse into how immigrants keep in touch with their homeland, 2010; MS083.008.027.00010; de Soto, Lucas
  - An examination of Somerville's 'local food movement' among the Brazilian population: a foreshadowing of their exclusion from the Green Line Extension, 2010; MS083.008.027.00011; Plitch, Rachael
  - Magoun Square past and present: ethnographies of immigrant business owners, 2010; MS083.008.027.00012; Weiss, Steven
- Fall 2011, MS083.009; 8 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials from the Fall 2011 semester.
  This series is arranged by project and material type.
  - Bridges and Barriers: Exploring the Supports and Setbacks of Immigrant Owned Restaurants in Somerville, 2011; MS083.009.001; Bean, Amy
    - Bridges and Barriers: Exploring the Supports and Setbacks of Immigrant Owned Restaurants in Somerville [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.001.00001; Bean, Amy
  - Brianna Brandon Project, 2011; MS083.009.002; Brandon, Brianna
    This project does not include a final report.
  - Processes of Inclusion and Exclusion in East Somerville, 2011; MS083.009.003; Chatterjee, Alicia
    - Processes of Inclusion and Exclusion in East Somerville [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.003.00001; Chatterjee, Alicia
  - Divergence and Unity: Community development projects and immigrant identities in Somerville, 2011; MS083.009.004; Fedele, Liana
    - Divergence and Unity: Community development projects and immigrant identities in Somerville [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.004.00001; Fedele, Liana
  - (Re)branding Somerville:Immigrant Business in a Changing Community, 2011; MS083.009.005; Kulig, Jessica
    - (Re)branding Somerville:Immigrant Business in a Changing Community [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.005.00001; Kulig, Jessica
  - Connectivity and City Government: Implications for Immigrant Owned Restaurant's in Somerville, 2011; MS083.009.006; Neff, Alexanne E.
    - Connectivity and City Government:Implications for Immigrant Owned Restaurant's in Somerville [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.006.00001; Neff, Alexanne E.
  - Customer Bases in Immigrant-Owned Restaurant Businesses in Somerville: Implications for Community Relations and Networks of Connectivity in Somerville, MA, 2011; MS083.009.007; Small, Rebecca
    - Customer Bases in Immigrant-Owned Restaurant Businesses in Somerville: Implications for Community Relations and Networks of Connectivity in Somerville, MA [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.007.00001; Small, Rebecca
  - The Processes of Creating an 'Internationally Friendly Culinary Area:' Assessing Cultural Tourism in Somerville, MA, 2011; MS083.009.008; Williams, Anna
    - The Processes of Creating an 'Internationally Friendly Culinary Area:' Assessing Cultural Tourism in Somerville, MA [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.008.00001; Williams, Anna
  - Stories of Somerville: An analysis of agency, structure, and culture amongst immigrant-owned food businesses in Union Square, 2011; MS083.009.009; Wyner, Emily
    - Stories of Somerville: An analysis of agency, structure, and culture amongst immigrant-owned food businesses in Union Square [Final Report], 2011; MS083.009.009.00001; Wyner, Emily
- Additional accessions, 2011; MS083.010; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Urban Borderlands class, Fall, 2011; MS083-002
- Website, 2011; MS083.000607; 1 Web sites
  This series is open for research.
  Website crawled by DCA to document the presence of Urban Borderlands on the web. The website in this series was crawled on a one-time basis.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Archived websites can be viewed online using the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine.
  - Urban Borderlands, 2011-02-10; MS083.000608; 1 Web sites